<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on 作业</title>
    <link>https://homework.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on 作业</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020 &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.wangchucheng.com/&#34;&gt;C. Wang&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ruiqima.com/&#34;&gt;R. Ma&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 13:34:38 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://homework.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A neural-network-based multi-function colour control method for four-colour light-emitting diodes - a solution for circadian effect</title>
      <link>https://homework.github.io/posts/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 13:34:38 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework.github.io/posts/second/</guid>
      <description>Based on the two main models of the spectral sensitivity function for the circadian system (𝐶𝐿𝐴 model and EML model), a multi-function light-emitting diode (LED) colour control method based on backpropagation artificial neural network (BP ANN) is proposed. The method can achieve colour control with high colour rendering indexes, high spectral circadian efficacy and low spectral circadian efficacy. The mixed-light method based on the flux contribution ratio provides data points for three spectral design strategies. These data points calculated by the software will be updated and utilized for the training of neural networks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change of circadian effect with colour temperature and eye spectral transmittance at different ages</title>
      <link>https://homework.github.io/posts/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Nov 2020 12:39:02 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://homework.github.io/posts/first/</guid>
      <description>摘要 With the recent advances in photobiology research and light-emitting diode technology, considering the circadian effects and the potential health benefits of lighting has attracted much attention. In this work, to achieve a white light-emitting LED cluster with beneficial and tunable circadian effects, a red-green-blue-warm white colour-mixing method based on pulse width modulation has been introduced and developed. Five optimal spectral power distributions were achieved with the correlated colour temperatures of 2700, 4000, 5000, 6500 and 8000K that provide maximum colour-rendering indices of 95.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
